Profile

A senior CS student and a Full stack engineer with a balanced range of experience between front-end and back-end technologies.

I'm driven by starting new projects from scratch and achieving engineering excellence in the products I ship

Skills

•••••

Contact

- ☆ GIZA, EGYPT
- **C** 0111 500 7982
- in https://bit.ly/3PbLGEK
- nttps://bit.ly/3PgJbkD
- % https://mahmoudhaney.me/

MAHMOUD HANAEY

Experience

Software Engineer Intern alx_africa | Jan 2023 - Apr 2023

Backend Developer Intern

Information Technology Institute (ITI) | Oct 2022 - Oct 2022

Entrepreneurship Trainee ITIDA - TIEC | Oct 2022 - 1 Week

Trainee - Job Market Skills
Nile University - AGYA| Sep 2022 - 1 Week

Volunteer

Cancer Hospital 57357 | Apr 2021 - Aug 2022

Education

Bachelor, Computer Science
Helwan University, Cairo | 2020 - Present

High School Diploma, Scientific-Math Al-Fadila School, Giza | 2017 - 2020

Projects

, , , , , ,	
2023	LIBRARY MANAGEMENT SYSTEM Python · Django ↑ https://bit.ly/462FxRr
2023	EARY SYSTEM React · NodeJS · MYSQL · APIs ↑ https://bit.ly/3PdApEb
2023	VOTING WEBSITE NodeJS · MYSQL · APIs ↑ https://bit.ly/3JdtXs0
2023	TRAFFIC SIGN RECOGNITION AI · ML · DL · Python · GUI https://bit.ly/3CsiVMH

FACE RECOGNITION

Al · ML · DL · Python · GUI

https://bit.ly/3NuqZTb